<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-04-03T21:42:24-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Hi-Res Media Group</title><subtitle>Graphic + Website Design, Digital Marketing - Corpus Christi, TX</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Post Test</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post Test" /><published>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</published><updated>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome/"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">To accompany the opening of their groundbreaking exhibit, The Color of Being/ El Color del Ser: DOROTHY HOOD (1918-2000), the Art Museum of South Texas commissioned us to design this activity book for their educational outreach programs. Using Texas artist Dorothy Hood’s rich color palette, 'Meet Dorothy Hood' tells the story of Dorothy Hood’s life and work, and inspires kids to ignite the artists within themselves.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/amst-1.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Post Test</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post Test" /><published>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</published><updated>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-3/"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">To accompany the opening of their groundbreaking exhibit, The Color of Being/ El Color del Ser: DOROTHY HOOD (1918-2000), the Art Museum of South Texas commissioned us to design this activity book for their educational outreach programs. Using Texas artist Dorothy Hood’s rich color palette, 'Meet Dorothy Hood' tells the story of Dorothy Hood’s life and work, and inspires kids to ignite the artists within themselves.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/amst-1.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Importance of Digital Marketing for Industrial Companies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Importance of Digital Marketing for Industrial Companies" /><published>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</published><updated>2017-03-18T17:16:01-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/new-years-eve-is-awesome-2/">&lt;p&gt;Digital marketing is not just for retail companies. Every buyer’s journey, B2B and B2C, often includes stops along the digital highway. Consumers of all types look for company and product reviews, search for different information, and educate themselves before heading into a sale. Digital marketing has outpaced analog solutions for several years, and the gap will only widen as more and more people turn to the internet as the first stop for information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;common-digital-marketing-avenues&quot;&gt;Common Digital Marketing Avenues&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the change in the way people connect, communicate and consume media, it should be no surprise that digital marketing is an essential part of any business strategy. Consider the simple fact that even the users who get online the least spend more than four hours each day online. Businesses that don’t connect with their customer base through preferred methods miss opportunities. Remember, digital marketing doesn’t just mean banner ads. It encompasses a complete range avenues including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Search (paid and organic)
Social media
Paid advertisements
Video ads
Apps and push notifications
Business profiles
Product reviews
And lots more!
If the content is available digitally, it is a part of an overall digital marketing strategy. Whether a business sells to the general consumer or makes products specifically for manufacturing, the importance of digital marketing is clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;how-do-businesses-shop&quot;&gt;How Do Businesses Shop?&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manufacturing companies and other businesses have something in common: people. People still make the purchasing decisions, and they do it by shopping using the avenues they are most comfortable with. Today, that means using online search tools and word of mouth spread through social media. A manufacturing company looking for a new supplier might ask for a recommendation on LinkedIn. Armed with a short list of candidates, the buyer might look at profile pages and collect feedback, all before making that first contact. If an industrial company hasn’t set up a well-rounded and engaging online presence, buyers are likely to look elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;how-to-use-digital-marketing-to-expand-industrial-opportunities&quot;&gt;How to Use Digital Marketing to Expand Industrial Opportunities&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital marketing can impact multiple levels of a business. From recruiting top talent to establishing a reputation for expertise and excellence, digital is the way to go. The challenge lies in putting together a strategy that works. All content should be aligned to that strategy. Any blog posts must lead back to the overall story being told, all without being a sales pitch. Digital marketing is not posting ads. It is developing an online presence that adds value for customers. A business that sells machine parts might post content about streamlining the manufacturing process or cutting costs with sustainable solutions. A business that supplies construction companies might create content surrounding building codes or best practices specific to the industry. The goal of all good marketing is to stay relevant, add value and position the company for maximum exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Industrial companies don’t need to worry about mass market appeal, but they do need exposure within their niche. No pop-up ads on a game app, but some native advertising on industry sites can go a long way. Blog content that explores the buyer’s journey and delves into pain points or videos that simplify complex concepts can all be helpful. Of course, social media is an integral part of B2B sales and marketing, as it is where many businesses can establish a reputation and start communicating with prospects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether a company needs a new recruitment strategy, better community outreach or to draw in more prospects, digital marketing has a solution that can help.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Digital marketing is not just for retail companies. Every buyer’s journey, B2B and B2C, often includes stops along the digital highway. Consumers of all types look for company and product reviews, search for different information, and educate themselves before heading into a sale. Digital marketing has outpaced analog solutions for several years, and the gap will only widen as more and more people turn to the internet as the first stop for information.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-digital-marketing-for-industrial-companies.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Key To Content Creation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-key-to-content-creation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Key To Content Creation" /><published>2016-07-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-07-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-key-to-content-creation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-key-to-content-creation/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;storytelling-the-key-to-content-creation&quot;&gt;Storytelling: The Key to Content Creation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an engagement officer for TAMU-CC, part of my responsibility is to facilitate the online presence of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.islanderalumni.org&quot;&gt;Islander Alumni Association&lt;/a&gt;, which includes social media and website updates. To accomplish this task, it is important for me to understand how social media will support the goals of the organization which are: furthering the alumni brand, engaging with alumni and students, and promoting a lifelong relationship between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tamucc.edu&quot;&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M University - Corpus Christi&lt;/a&gt; and its growing number of alumni. Most people maintain a personal profile on at least one major networking platform such as Facebook, Instagram or Twitter, and are a great way for people to express their individuality and share their life with friends and family. This is no different for a business or organization. Social media networks are now the go-to platforms for many businesses and organizations to connect with their audience and promote their brands; however, there is much more to managing a successful social media platform for a business or organization. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrmg.agency/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/13221074_1158777970822788_8111733889534729852_n-e1467655434204.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.hrmg.agency/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/13221074_1158777970822788_8111733889534729852_n-e1467655434204-300x206.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Islander Graduation Photo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In creating content for your organization, start at the bottom. A good foundation to support these goals is to have a great a content strategy. Everyone has a different approach when it comes to creating engaging content, but one of the most effective ways is to tell a story. A great story is short and to the point and often includes various characters that take on different roles. A great story also has elements of emotion, tension, and overcoming obstacles. Creating content for the Islander Alumni Association’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/islanderalumni&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt; is no different. We have various events that happen throughout the year and we create our social media content accordingly. For example, during the weeks leading up to homecoming, we focus on the history of our university and create engaging content by hosting online photo sharing events, contests, upcoming events and videos. In general, the most specific you can get with your content plan, the more effective you’ll be in its implementation. This is why content planning is essential to your online success, so it is good practice to spend the time creating the content. Consider having the following procedures in place when planning and publishing content:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Establish policies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creation procedures&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Content framework/matrix&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Calendar creation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Editorial approval&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Publishing procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, every action you take online, whether it be a business website or social network, is part of a telling your organization’s story. Your content should be guided by a plan that will help reach pre-determined goals.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Storytelling: The Key to Content Creation</summary></entry></feed>